html.net 2008-06-15

# Privacy statement | HTML.net

This privacy statement was last updated on 23 December 2005.

Your privacy is important to HTML.net. We have created this privacy statement in order to disclose our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site, www.html.net. Upon reading this privacy statement, you will know:

  * What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information is collected
  * The organization collecting the information
  * How the information is used
  * With whom the information may be shared
  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
  * The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the HTML.net webmaster by emailing or writing to us at the following address:

Flensborggade 30, st.tv  
1669 Copenhagen V  
Denmark

If you feel that HTML.net has not complied with the policies outlined in this privacy statement please contact us.

HTML.net and [OUTPUT I/S](http://www.output.dk/?lang=en) are the sole owners of the information it gathers on its site. We will only share your information with outside parties in ways that are described in this privacy statement or if we are required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law, cooperate with law enforcement agencies, or comply with a legal process served on our web site.

## What information is collected and how it is used?

### HTML.net news alert service

We collect contact information such as name and email address. This information is used to generate a newsletter for you each time the HTML.net website is updated with news. The information requested will solely be used for HTML.net's own purposes.

### Contact us

We use a contact form located on the "Contact HTML.net" page and other areas of the site to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have. We read every message sent in and try to reply promptly to every one. This information is used to respond directly to your questions or comments. We may use your comments to improve the site and program, and we may either keep your comments on file or review and discard them. This information is shared with third parties only with your explicit permission.

### Logged files

The HTML.net web site logs IP addresses and browser types for systems administration purposes. These logs will be analyzed to improve the value of the materials available on the website. A user's session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous. We do not link IP addresses to any personally identifiable information.

### Links

The HTML.net web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that these web sites' privacy policies may differ from those of HTML.net. HTML.net is not endorsing the products and/or services of the site to which the link is made.

## Choices regarding the use of your information

### How to unsubscribe from the HTML.net news alert service

To unsubscribe from receiving the HTML.net news alert, an unsubscribe link appears at the end of each email and when you click on it you will be transfered to a page where you can cancel your subscribtion.

### Notification of changes

If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection through this web site, we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already collected through our site, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change.

* * *

* * *
